export const chapter16StudyData = [
  // Key Terms
  {
    id: "KT1601",
    front: "asylum",
    back: "institution created for the specific purpose of housing people with psychological disorders"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1602",
    front: "aversive conditioning",
    back: "counterconditioning technique that pairs an unpleasant stimulant with an undesirable behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1603",
    front: "behavior therapy",
    back: "therapeutic orientation that employs principles of learning to help clients change undesirable behaviors"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1604",
    front: "biomedical therapy",
    back: "treatment that involves medication and/or medical procedures to treat psychological disorders"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1605",
    front: "cognitive therapy",
    back: "form of psychotherapy that focuses on how a person's thoughts lead to feelings of distress, with the aim of helping them change these irrational thoughts"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1606",
    front: "cognitive-behavioral therapy",
    back: "form of psychotherapy that aims to change cognitive distortions and self-defeating behaviors"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1607",
    front: "comorbid disorder",
    back: "individual who has two or more diagnoses, which often includes a substance abuse diagnosis and another psychiatric diagnosis, such as depression, bipolar disorder, or schizophrenia"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1608",
    front: "confidentiality",
    back: "therapist cannot disclose confidential communications to any third party, unless mandated or permitted by law"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1609",
    front: "counterconditioning",
    back: "classical conditioning therapeutic technique in which a client learns a new response to a stimulus that has previously elicited an undesirable behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1610",
    front: "couples therapy",
    back: "two people in an intimate relationship, such as husband and wife, who are having difficulties and are trying to resolve them with therapy"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1611",
    front: "cultural competence",
    back: "therapist's understanding and attention to issues of race, culture, and ethnicity in providing treatment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1612",
    front: "deinstitutionalization",
    back: "process of closing large asylums and integrating people back into the community where they can be treated locally"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1613",
    front: "dream analysis",
    back: "technique in psychoanalysis in which patients recall their dreams and the psychoanalyst interprets them to reveal unconscious desires or struggles"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1614",
    front: "electroconvulsive therapy (ECT)",
    back: "type of biomedical therapy that involves using an electrical current to induce seizures in a person to help alleviate the effects of severe depression"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1615",
    front: "exposure therapy",
    back: "counterconditioning technique in which a therapist seeks to treat a client's fear or anxiety by presenting the feared object or situation with the idea that the person will eventually get used to it"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1616",
    front: "family therapy",
    back: "special form of group therapy consisting of one or more families"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1617",
    front: "free association",
    back: "technique in psychoanalysis in which the patient says whatever comes to mind at the moment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1618",
    front: "group therapy",
    back: "treatment modality in which 5-10 people with the same issue or concern meet together with a trained clinician"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1619",
    front: "humanistic therapy",
    back: "therapeutic orientation aimed at helping people become more self-aware and accepting of themselves"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1620",
    front: "individual therapy",
    back: "treatment modality in which the client and clinician meet one-on-one"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1621",
    front: "intake",
    back: "therapist's first meeting with the client in which the therapist gathers specific information to address the client's immediate needs"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1622",
    front: "involuntary treatment",
    back: "therapy that is mandated by the courts or other systems"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1623",
    front: "nondirective therapy",
    back: "therapeutic approach in which the therapist does not give advice or provide interpretations but helps the person identify conflicts and understand feelings"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1624",
    front: "play therapy",
    back: "therapeutic process, often used with children, that employs toys to help them resolve psychological problems"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1625",
    front: "psychoanalysis",
    back: "therapeutic orientation developed by Sigmund Freud that employs free association, dream analysis, and transference to uncover repressed feelings"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1626",
    front: "psychotherapy (also, psychodynamic psychotherapy)",
    back: "psychological treatment that employs various methods to help someone overcome personal problems, or to attain personal growth"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1627",
    front: "rational emotive therapy (RET)",
    back: "form of cognitive-behavioral therapy"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1628",
    front: "relapse",
    back: "repeated drug use and/or alcohol use after a period of improvement from substance abuse"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1629",
    front: "Rogerian (client-centered therapy)",
    back: "non-directive form of humanistic psychotherapy developed by Carl Rogers that emphasizes unconditional positive regard and self-acceptance"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1630",
    front: "strategic family therapy",
    back: "therapist guides the therapy sessions and develops treatment plans for each family member for specific problems that can addressed in a short amount of time"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1631",
    front: "structural family therapy",
    back: "therapist examines and discusses with the family the boundaries and structure of the family: who makes the rules, who sleeps in the bed with whom, how decisions are made, and what are the boundaries within the family"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1632",
    front: "systematic desensitization",
    back: "form of exposure therapy used to treat phobias and anxiety disorders by exposing a person to the feared object or situation through a stimulus hierarchy"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1633",
    front: "token economy",
    back: "controlled setting where individuals are reinforced for desirable behaviors with tokens (e.g., poker chip) that be exchanged for items or privileges"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1634",
    front: "transference",
    back: "process in psychoanalysis in which the patient transfers all of the positive or negative emotions associated with the patient's other relationships to the psychoanalyst"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1635",
    front: "unconditional positive regard",
    back: "fundamental acceptance of a person regardless of what they say or do; term associated with humanistic psychology"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1636",
    front: "virtual reality exposure therapy",
    back: "uses a simulation rather than the actual feared object or situation to help people conquer their fears"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1637",
    front: "voluntary treatment",
    back: "therapy that a person chooses to attend in order to obtain relief from her symptoms"
  },
  // Review Questions
  {
    id: "R1601",
    front: "Who of the following does not support the humane and improved treatment of mentally ill persons?",
    back: "medieval priests"
  },
  {
    id: "R1602",
    front: "The process of closing large asylums and providing for people to stay in the community to be treated locally is known as ________.",
    back: "deinstitutionalization"
  },
  {
    id: "R1603",
    front: "Joey was convicted of domestic violence. As part of his sentence, the judge has ordered that he attend therapy for anger management. This is considered ________ treatment.",
    back: "involuntary"
  },
  {
    id: "R1604",
    front: "Today, most people with psychological problems are not hospitalized. Typically they are only hospitalized if they ________.",
    back: "are an imminent threat to themselves or others"
  },
  {
    id: "R1605",
    front: "The idea behind ________ is that how you think determines how you feel and act.",
    back: "cognitive therapy"
  },
  {
    id: "R1606",
    front: "Mood stabilizers, such as lithium, are used to treat ________.",
    back: "bipolar disorder"
  },
  {
    id: "R1607",
    front: "Clay is in a therapy session. The therapist asks him to relax and say whatever comes to his mind at the moment. This therapist is using ________, which is a technique of ________.",
    back: "free association; psychoanalysis"
  },
  {
    id: "R1608",
    front: "A treatment modality in which 5-10 people with the same issue or concern meet together with a trained clinician is known as ________.",
    back: "group therapy"
  },
  {
    id: "R1609",
    front: "What happens during an intake?",
    back: "The therapist gathers specific information to address the client's immediate needs such as the presenting problem, the client's support system, and insurance status. The therapist informs the client about confidentiality, fees, and what to expect in a therapy session."
  },
  {
    id: "R1610",
    front: "What is the minimum amount of time addicts should receive treatment if they are to achieve a desired outcome?",
    back: "3 months"
  },
  {
    id: "R1611",
    front: "When an individual has two or more diagnoses, which often includes a substance-related diagnosis and another psychiatric diagnosis, this is known as ________.",
    back: "comorbid disorder"
  },
  {
    id: "R1612",
    front: "John was drug-free for almost six months. Then he started hanging out with his addict friends, and he has now started abusing drugs again. This is an example of ________.",
    back: "relapse"
  },
  {
    id: "R1613",
    front: "The sociocultural perspective looks at you, your behaviors, and your symptoms in the context of your ________.",
    back: "culture and background"
  },
  {
    id: "R1614",
    front: "Which of the following was not listed as a barrier to mental health treatment?",
    back: "being a member of the ethnic majority"
  }
];